So it's looking moist.
It's looking delicious.
We've got our two pages, but, um.
Yeah, that's, uh, not so good.
So there's one little neaten this up a little bit before we show you how to link the two pages together.
So we need to move this one across a little bit to his position here.
And then we need to add in something which I bet is going to be a what a recipe.
Yeah a recipe.
And that's going to go here in any little table that's going to help us do that.
Um, so first thing is, how in the world are we going to move that across there?
Okay.
So there are there are not many ways to do that in HTML.
Yeah.
So if we're using CSS yeah.
Then you've got a lot more options.
But this is not a CSS course.
There's very complicated ways to do an HTML.
They should do CSS course and then the JavaScript course.
Yeah but that's next.
This is what you've got to get right.
First this is HTML basics.
So we got to we got to hack it a little bit here.
Okay.
So um what we're going to want to add, which is very simple, but it seems like the kind of uneffective
just take a break.
Take a you're going to do this.
it'll be in HTML and we don't want to go into some hard stuff doing this.
Yeah.
So we've got to move this this cake across, you know, and we can center it.
But that's only going to center it in the cell.
So so we need to do so we've got some spaces essentially.
So we you know if we do that doesn't do anything that's not going to do squat.
We've got this little thing called the ampersand l b s p which is a non-breaking space a non-breaking
space okay.
So now okay let's see what happens.
So you put a Non-breaking space.
Let's save that.
Yeah.
Let's check it out.
Refresh.
It moved across about a millimetre.
Yeah.
So not much going on.
This is where you're going to be like wait, what?
I think you want to copy that.
Yeah.
Paste it in what two of them paste a lot and a lot and a lot.
Oh wow.
So you're creating lots of little spaces in there.
Yeah.
Because it is going to be very complicated either way even though it looks uneffective.
But that's it.
We're gonna get a little go.
Across the screen.
Yeah, just like that.
So it's a bit of a sort of hacky way of doing it using HTML.
Uh, but yeah, it works.
So essentially all we've done is we've now just stuck a whole lot of little spaces in here.
It's basically just trying to make it, uh.
And so again, if you wanted to put more in just however, you mean you need to get it just so it's
perfect, keep hitting refresh and you can say, yep, that is just spot on.
Okay.
So that's not bad.
It's sitting there.
It's looking pretty.
Pretty cool and dandy.
Yep.
So now we want to put in our recipe.
Yeah that's got to go on that side.
So we're going to need another we need another TD.
So second column in.
There we go.
Here we go.
Hit that.
Hit the tab.
Hit it.
Yeah okay.
So we don't really know cake recipes or what do you mean cake recipe.
So we use the lovely Google Google cake recipe search.
And this isn't a carrot cake.
But yeah we can make this into carrot cake.
Yeah.
We just go like that.
We don't.
Yeah.
I mean, if any of you guys know a good carrot cake recipe, you can help us later.
But, I mean, we're gonna we HTML guys.
Yeah, yeah, we eat carrot cake.
We're not gonna try and make it, so we're gonna.
We need a we're gonna put that in.
But before we do that, we've seen Google's also done this.
Oh, yeah.
One.
Two three.
Okay, so this this whole list thing and a ordered list.
Okay.
Yeah.
We want an ordered list.
Fantastic tablet in space.
Oh, yeah, I hit the tab.
Okay, then inside our ordered list, we want our list items.
Yeah.
All right.
So and we're going to have to put a few allies in here.
It's just going to be one because it's one list and then stick in.
Yeah.
So just put that in the items that are going to go in there.
Okay.
So let's just go there.
We just this is looking pretty messy.
Let's just just use a little command hack.
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay.
This is getting really messy right now.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
You got it.
Oh, no I don't.
I'm going too far.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, we can do this.
Almost got it.
There we go.
Tap it in.
Tap it in, baby.
There we go.
Looking a little bit better there.
Um, okay, so we got to break this up.
Yeah.
So each one has to be a list item.
So let's just take that command x.
So it's going to end.
That one ends right there.
That's our first list.
We create another list.
I would say it ends after the dots because that's a nine inch.
Yeah because that's also in.
But yeah let's just stick them at the end of each line or something there.
Oh yeah.
Stick it there.
And then the second list over there.
Oh let's let's just do ourselves a favor here and just use our little command.
Yeah.
Do it all together.
Um, I'll, uh, stop it there.
And then at the end of each one, close off the lists.
Yeah.
So we're going to close it.
All are closed.
Right.
So they've now all been made part of our ordered list.
Let's take a look at that.
Ah, that's looking much better.
Okay.
So, um, we are going to need to space this out a bit because as you can see, also what they've done
is when it's got too long, you just you it's wrapping you b r so you break the line so we can see where
does it go too long this fluffy one.
So sugar I say that's where we break it until.
Okay.
So we go to here until put in BR save that.
You notice now it's not going to be really long.
So now it's going to put it in two lines again after water.
Yeah.
Um where's water.
Water.
Yeah b r that.
So you can see everything requires this is you coding.
You are actually having to specify all the little details.
Now a lot of this, there are some shortcuts around it when you are starting to use CSS, but it's really
useful for you to learn how to do it all, basically like in HTML, because later on when you do get
more advanced, you need to understand the basics.
Yeah.
So that's looking good.
Except, um, we've got to move that across.
So what's the plan?
We're going to have to space that out.
But if we put in like we've got with these spaces right here, if we put it in there, it's going to
get very confused because now it's like, which one must I put a whole bunch of spaces to.
So rather than that we're going to add in another table.
So we've got another column.
Okay.
We're going to add another.
And then that's going to have a lot of spaces in that column.
So you won't be able to see.
So basically all we're doing is we're going to add in a column between the two that's going to go here.
And we're just going to then put in a whole bunch of spaces.
Okay.
Now see there we go.
Okay, so we've actually got a blank column in the middle there.
You can adjust the size of that middle column however many spaces you want, but that looks maybe take
out a few.
Let's just go here.
Oh stop about there.
Let's see if it's looking good.
Such a perfectionist okay okay.
So there we go.
That's looking pretty good I think.
Um, so we're getting pretty close to having this unbelievably mastered and awesome website.
I'm going to show you one more thing that you're going to do.
We'll do that in the next video.
But you're going to have to be patient for that.
I'll show you how you can actually add a video to your page.
That would be really cool.
Video of someone making the cake.
How cool would that be?
And then all that's left is to link it all up.
So really close over to you, see if you can make your second page look a little bit nicer.
Um, add in the images, move them across, try and align them and see how it all works for you.
So stop watching and start doing.
Remember our famous quote?
You know those quotes we liked about education?
Yeah.
How much you learn from doing well?
Get out there and do.